maxfoundry.com 2012-05-24

# Privacy Policy | Max Foundry

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to our email lists, and when you join our affiliate program. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

## What is the information used for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience; your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * To improve our website; we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * To improve customer service; your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To process transactions; your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails; the email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## How do we protect the information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit card information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## Data storage

We use third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run the Max Foundry website. However, we own all the code and databases used to run the Max Foundry website.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page and send an email notifying you of any changes.

This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 5, 2010.

Questions and inquiries about this Privacy Policy can be directed to [support@maxfoundry.com](mailto:support@maxfoundry.com).
